<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="help_questions">
        <item>1.&#160;How does One Security protect my mobile?</item>
        <item>2.&#160;What are One Security VIP functions?</item>
        <item>3.&#160;How to upgrade to VIP users?</item>
        <item>4.&#160;How to get one-month FREE VIP trial?</item>
        <item>5.&#160;What is the \"Scan\" button in the main interface for?</item>
        <item>6.&#160;How to prevent mobile phone from viruses?</item>
        <item>7.&#160;What is the \"Go\" for?</item>
        <item>8.&#160;What is the \"Manage Running Apps\" for?</item>
        <item>9.&#160;What is Privacy Space for?</item>
        <item>10.&#160;Why can\'t I import photos in Privacy Space?</item>
        <item>11.&#160;How to upgrade the One Security manually?</item>
        <item>12.&#160;How to send feedback?</item>
        <item>13.&#160;How to turn off the icon on the status bar?</item>
    </string-array>
    
    <string-array name="help_answers">
        <item>One Security is a utility designed to keep your mobile and data safe from potential malicious internet attacks. It uses Tencent patent-pending cloud-based virus scan technology, certificated by most prestigious AV-Comparatives &#038; West coast Labs Checkmark, thus One Security can quickly and accurately identify and remove emerging threats from viruses and malware.</item>
        <item>The standard features apply for both basic and VIP users.Upgrading to VIP entitles you to premium features:\n1)&#160;Up to date virus database protects your mobile from all latest threats.Upgrade to VIP for automatic virus database upgrades.\n2)&#160;Personal Privacy Space to keep your notes and photos more private.</item>
        <item>First, you need to enter VIP Zone, and click \"Get More Days\", then make the payment by following instructions. After successful payment you will become a VIP user and enjoy all exclusive features.</item>
        <item>First, enter VIP Zone, then click \"30 Days FREE Trial\" to apply for free VIP trial through sharing One Security via SMS. After sharing with 5 friends via SMS, you can get one-month free VIP trial for all VIP features.</item>
        <item>You can click \"Scan\" on the main interface to perform a quick antivirus scan. This process will quickly detect risks if there are potential vulnerable malware and viruses in your mobile. And then you can choose whether to remove them to make your mobile safe.</item>
        <item>Scanning viruses regularly is an effective way to protect your mobile. By clicking \"Scan\", you can quickly scan the most vulnerable part of the mobile to protect it from virus infection. And \"Full Scan\" can scan your mobile thoroughly and remove detected viruses.</item>
        <item>By clicking \"Go\", One Security will clean up the phone cache, terminate unnecessary processes, and improve the operating speed of your mobile system.</item>
        <item>With this feature, you can view and manage all running apps on your mobile. If you feel mobile response speed is slow than usual, you might want to stop some of those running apps.</item>
        <item>Privacy Space is a safe area for your enhanced data privacy. It can keep unlimited notes (for all users) and photos (exclusive for VIP) in a password-protected space and away from unauthorized access.</item>
        <item>To import photos into Privacy Space, you need to upgrade to be VIP users.</item>
        <item>Open Menu, and select \"About\", then click \"Update\". The app will be updated if there is a new version detected.</item>
        <item>Open menu, and select \"Feedback\". Input your advice or issues and click \"send\". Our service team would response your feedback shortly.</item>
        <item>Open menu, select \"Settings\" and switch off \"Icon on status bar\".</item>
    </string-array>
    
    
    <!-- 隐私监控数据。#1代表一种类型的隐私，后面是提示的MSG；
    		下面是Permission与#1的映射关系（多对多）。
		    -->
    <string-array name="privacy_msgs">
	    <item>#1:Access your Messages</item>
	    <item>#2:Access your Contacts</item>
	    <item>#3:Access your Call History</item>
	    <item>#4:Read your Identify Info</item>
	    <item>#5:Access your Calendar</item>
	    <item>#6:Access your Browser History</item>
	    <item>#7:Track your Location</item>
	    <item>#8:Record your Audio</item>
    </string-array>
    
    <string-array name="privacy_permission">
        <item>android.permission.READ_SMS,#1</item>
        <item>android.permission.WRITE_SMS,#1</item>
        <item>android.permission.RECEIVE_SMS,#1</item>
        <item>android.permission.SEND_SMS,#1</item>
        <item>android.permission.READ_CONTACTS,#2,#3</item>
        <item>android.permission.WRITE_CONTACTS,#2</item>        
        <item>android.permission.READ_PHONE_STATE,#4</item>        
        <item>android.permission.READ_CALENDAR,#5</item>
        <item>android.permission.WRITE_CALENDAR,#5</item>        
        <item>android.permission.READ_HISTORY_BOOKMARKS,#6</item>
        <item>android.permission.WRITE_HISTORY_BOOKMARKS,#6</item>
        <item>android.permission.ACCESS_COARSE_LOCATION,#7</item>
        <item>android.permission.ACCESS_FINE_LOCATION,#7</item>
        <item>android.permission.ACCESS_LOCATION_EXTRA_COMMANDS,#7</item>
        <item>android.permission.ACCESS_MOCK_LOCATION,#7</item>
        <item>android.permission.RECORD_AUDIO,#8</item>
        
    </string-array>
            <!-- 病毒扫描时广告信息 -->    <!-- 对应广告类型，用来区分图标 0普通，1病毒-->
    <string-array name="virus_advert">
        <item>More VIRUSES are spreading among Android mobiles. Scan everyday to keep it in good shape.#1</item>
        <item>One Security protects your mobile with Real-time and Cloud technology against latest threats.#0</item>
        <item>Get VIP to assure you are protected from the latest threats by downloading the latest virus engine.#0</item>
        <item>Privacy Space keeps your private information from being accessed by others.#0</item>
        <item>One-click Device Boost automatically stops all running apps to free up memory.#0</item>
    </string-array>
    <!-- 对应广告类型，用来区分图标 0普通，1病毒-->
</resources>
